Angel Beaversouris · he/they

Lynnwood, WA · (360) 524-4240 · a.beaversouris@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/angel-beaversouris · sushirocks.github.io Co-Owner at Beaversouris LLC, Software Development; 10+ years in Customer Service and Sales; Educated in Comm Sci, English, & Linguistics; DEI Advocate and Ally — Ask Me Anything!

LANGUAGES

English (multiple dialects)

2000 - Present

- Native & trained; professional-level Copywriting, Technical Writing, and Rhetoric of Language

American Sign Language

2016 - Present

- Conversational level, learned through academia, club events, and ASL chat nights.

EDUCATION

Western Washington University, Bellingham WA

Sept 2019 – March 2021

Bachelor of Communication Sciences and Disorders

GPA 3.8

- Minors in English and Linguistics
- Member of National Student Speech Language Hearing Association (NSSLHA)

Bellevue College, Bellevue WA

Jan 2016 – June 2019

Associate of Arts and Sciences

GPA 3.8

- Phi Theta Kappa Honors Society
 - Biology Student Outreach
 - American Sign Language Club

RELATED EXPERIENCE

Author, Textbroker International, Remote

Dec 2022 - Present

- Create original and engaging content on the fly on a topic provided to me
- Fulfill orders for clients within a consistent time frame

Speech Dept Coordinator, Evergreen Speech & Hearing Clinic, Inc., Bellevue, WA

Apr 2021 - Jul 2021

- Client-Provider Liaison and Scheduler for 1-6 providers
- Worked closely with supervisor to build out SLP schedules monthly.
- Led pediatric program recall scheduling and data management.
- Microsoft Outlook, Microsoft Teams, Zipwhip, Webex, CounselEar, Fax machines, copy machines, etc.

Copy Editor, Tolt Technologies LLC, Duvall, WA

Nov 2020 – Apr 2021

- Correct grammar, spelling and punctuation errors.
- Arrange page layouts to include written content as well as elements like photos and diagrams.
- Format and trim down grant applications.

Classroom Tutor, Whatcom Literacy Council, Bellingham WA

Feb 2020 – May 2020

- Tutored continuing-education adults and helped them obtain GED and High School Diploma
 - Focused on: Geography, Algebra, and English
- Assisted Small Group Coordinator and Lead Instructor in modifying lesson plans and pace for students

SKILLS

Service, Scouts

Writing, Author & Copy Editing, English BA Minor

2016 - Present

2009 - 2020

- Authoring/writing original material
- Line-editing documents and web pages
- Developmental editing for flow, accessibility, and comprehension level.

- Fundraising, Leadership, & Treasury Duties

Marketing, Customer Service, & Sales